Toon-chan! Toon-chan!
Ah, my fun! Call an ambulance now!
I... He didn't have to rush at me like that.
I was only trying to scare you so I could make a point.
Dan-chan!
Say something!
I'm fine, Mom.
You!
This is your fault!
I didn't want all of this to happen!
But no!
You just had to keep pushing me!
Like with this?
I'd kill myself for you!
Meanwhile, you're trying to build a life without me!
You won't even tell me who took the picture!
What?
No one took it!
Look!
You can see for yourself!
The camera has a timer!
And why should I?
Everything out of your mouth has been a lie!
All of it!
There's a timer!
Stop lying!
Right.
Go and get the picture!
I should be trying to save her, not a damn picture!
The cost is too great.
Without that photo, our present is gone.
Admit that you've been lying!
Admit that you're trying to replace me!
Jiji!
Give that to me!
I said give it!
You even turned my children against me!
Do you have any idea how much I've sacrificed for this family?
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry.
I couldn't see this coming.
I wouldn't have let you go if I had.
I wasn't dunno!
She needs help!
God, you're done.
I was telling you, I okay...
...
In a big, faraway forest, there was a small cabin, and in that cabin lived a family.
There was a father, a mother, and a pair of siblings, and they all lived happily together
in their forest home.
Then, one day, the brother took his sister into the forest to collect berries, and when
they were done, night had fallen.
They got lost in the dark, and the sister got scared.
Then, they came across two crows who could speak, so they asked for directions.
But, the crows only laughed at their plight, so the brother, angered by the crows mocking
them, killed one with a stone, causing the other to fly away.
Brother chased it into the night, and he chased, and he chased.
All through the night, he chased, never stopping to rest.
That's enough for now.
It's time for bed.
You too, Shishi.
See you tomorrow.
Hey, Mom.
Do the siblings in your story ever find their way back home?
Had enough?
Well, have you?
Have you?
Yes, hello?
I need to report a crime.
My next-door neighbor is beating his wife.
They're at 48 Tongli Lane, room 607 in the Nanda District.
You need to send someone now.
I think he's going to kill her.
That was your last goddamn mistake, you worthless piece of trash.
Get out.
I tried to give you a chance, but now you've gone past the point of forgiveness.
I'm going to remind you that you're mine.
You stupid bitch.
Hurry!
So, Josh, shut up.
What did you learn?
What happened?
You stopped responding.
Don't really know.
One minute, everything went black.
Now I'm here.
That's it.
How is that?
Don't you control when you leave?
Yeah, but I clap like how I go in.
And I might not have.
My last memory doesn't make sense.
I was looking at Shishi's dad, but it was like I was in her mother's body.
The rest is blank.
This has never happened before.
It's strange.
Is that it?
What about before?
What did you learn?
Anything is helpful.
Captain, please be patient.
He needs time to recover.
Right, sorry.
I'll consolidate everything that we know so far.
I'll talk to my people.
Confirm it's her in the photo.
The report said she and her husband were both found dead in their apartment.
Their neighbor had called the police.
He said they'd been fighting, and he was worried that Li Lan's life was in danger.
They died shortly after the call.
Forensics showed that Li Lan killed her husband with a blow to the head from a hammer.
Li Lan died from a stab wound to the abdomen.
Their children, Li Tianxian, and his twin sister, Li Tianxie, were found in the apartment.
That sounds like what I saw, but it doesn't line up.
Li Lan was being abused for years.
Why suddenly fight back?
Who knows?
You left right before.
Probably hit a breaking point.
Hey, what about the two children?
They knew about the photograph.
Maybe one of them could help us out.
That's a dead end.
If we had files, they're gone.
They've been ghosts since their parents' deaths.
Wait.
There's an informant, but you're the only one they'll talk to.
Says they know the truth.
Me?
Yes, they're waiting for you at the station.
Then let's go.
Hey, wait a second.
Something about this feels off.
You should be careful.
It's a police station.
What could happen?
Don't worry.
Chao Ling, keep an eye on him for me.
Just in case.
You need to be careful, too.
The killer is still out there.
There's no telling what he'll do.
I'll arrange for a new guard rotation.
Let's go.
Hmm?
I'll give you a rundown on how to talk to the witness on the ride over to the station.
Right.
She didn't have anything on her.
Not even a phone.
We've been trying to see what we could learn before you arrived.
But she made it clear that she will not talk to anyone unless it's you.
She won't remove her mask or let us take anything we could use for a background check.
Hell, we had to remove all the monitoring devices in the room before she'd say anything.
So don't let her know that you're wired or she'll shut down.
Right.
Let's get you bugged, okay?
Shouldn't I have something so I can hear you?
Maybe an earpiece?
That's harder to hide.
And she walked in here not trusting us.
I'm sorry.
It's too risky.
Just stick to what we covered on the way here.
You set the rhythm.
If you do that, you've got control.
You got this.
Now go and crack this case wide open.
What all me?
Fine.
All right.
You got me.
Can I at least know your name?
Sure.
It's Li Tien-xie.
Li Tien-xie?
It's been a long time coming.
Good to meet you.
First, get rid of whatever they hit on you.
It can't be.
Bring me everything you've found on Li Tien-xie.
Everything we have is right here.
That's it.
There's nothing else on me.
Really?
How considerate of you.
I'd still like to check for myself.
All right.
Seems like you're trustworthy enough.
That's a decent place to start things off, I think.
Oh, hey.
Can you hold on to this?
Now that we trust each other, you mind telling me what you know or why we're meeting at a police station?
Every game has to be a fair give and take.
So now I'm giving.
You've played games before, right?
It's you.
This will be your punishment for breaking the rules.
And now, we get to reset the board.
So she's the one who's been controlling people.
But I thought she was mute.
I'm sorry for what happened.
I wish...
Happened?
How would you know anything that's happened to me?
You did flinch when you heard my name.
I see.
You know something at the very least.
Which begs the question.
How do you know?
Crap.
I have no way of knowing if this is Li Tien-xie or if she's possessed.
It's too dangerous to mention how I actually learned about what happened.
I'll have to think of how the police might already know.
I said don't lie.
Seems your first punishment wasn't enough to get you to stop cheating.
See, you can fool me.
But she sees right through you.
No.
I still don't know how she knew I was lying last time.
I can't risk doing it again.
Go on then.
Don't leave me waiting.
I know about your past because of that photograph you gave to us.
There.
Isn't the truth refreshing?
Speaking of,
this was a big step forward.
We should celebrate...
with a soda!
Huh?
Thanks.
Here, I got three cans.
Thank you.
I really appreciate this.
Is there a way for you to enjoy yourself that's not as disgusting?
That's just what I needed.
Soda's the best, isn't it?
Hey, if you don't mind me asking,
why do you wear that mask?
Ah, look, no judgment.
Just curious.
It looks uncomfortable,
especially in such a stuffy room.
I'm not sick.
I've never been sick.
The world is different for me.
I don't know why,
but since I was a kid,
I've always been sensitive to things others aren't.
A light breeze sounds like screaming in my ears.
Dog barks are painful.
Even a puppy sounds like a roaring monster.
And when people look at me,
it feels like ants are crawling underneath my skin.
I'm always tense.
It kept me from speaking for a long time.
My mom did her best to help me.
That's amazing.
Great job, Shishi.
It seemed impossible.
But little by little,
the world stopped hurting so much.
Until that night...
It wouldn't help Shishi anyway.
Even if we had the money,
she doesn't need a program.
She needs to learn how to be a good wife and mother.
Or how not to be one.
Hers can't stop batting her eyes at any man
she happens to come across.
I lost everything after that.
Now the only way I feel safe
is if I cover up as much of my body
as I possibly can.
I'm tired of people looking at me
and seeing a freak
when I'm just trying to survive.
I'm sorry.
I don't think you're a freak.
If you're honestly sorry,
then you should make it up to me.
What is it now?
The soda went right through her
and now she needs the restroom.
Fine, let's go.
About that,
she's still kind of skittish.
So yeah,
it's best if it's just me.
All right, be quick.
Go down the hall,
take the first left,
then go to the end.
I can show them.
Stay with them
until they're both back in the room
and keep your guard up.
She may try something.
Come on, this way.
Come on.
I'll have to go in with you.
Hold on.
Do me a favor.
Will you answer my question first?
Yeah, I guess.
This can't be everything
we have on them.
There should be a paper trail
documenting what happened to them
after the investigation.
So where is it?
Captain,
I'm worried for Officer Wong.
Shouldn't she have some backup?
Yeah,
she can handle this herself.
I wouldn't have sent her in alone
if I doubted her.
It's just Li Tianxi
is whispering something,
but I can't make it out.
I hear it too.
I'm sure Officer Wong
will fill us in.
Jenshin.
What?
What was that?
Speak up.
One more time.
I said...
Jenshin was Li'd on the case?
Captain,
something weird's going on.
Damn it.
That's no coincidence.
The case was the same year
he left the Force.
Hmm.
You showed up right after
we left the room.
And you knew the exact reason
why I asked to leave.
So who else is listening,
Officer?
Damn it.
She caught us.
Ugh.
This is my fault.
I sent Wong Juan
in way too early.
But why tip her hand?
Is she still connected
to Jenshin somehow?
Could he be pulling
the strings on all of this?
But to what end?
Captain,
I'm gonna go and check on them.
I'll come too.
Hold on.
Look, Wong's gone.
What happened?
I'm sorry, Captain Xiao.
We went inside
and the window was out.
Thought that maybe
he had an accident.
We've secured the room,
but he's not here.
Right.
It's time to go.
I won't be losing
so easily
this time around.
Officer Wong!
Cheng Xiaoshis!
You in here?
Officer Wong!
Cheng Xiaoshis!
Captain Xiao,
no one's here.
They're gone.
It's Wong Juan.
She took them.
I'm going after her.
Officer Wong!
What in the world
is happening here?
She took them.
But why?
It doesn't make sense.
Where would she go?
No time to wonder.
First, we get them back.
Then,
we get some answers.
yours.